[upbeat music]
（欢快的音乐）
- Let's laser tag it up!
——让我们来一场激光对战吧！
- Yay, fresh meat.
——耶，新鲜血液。
- Yep. Sign us up, Lucy.
——是的。给我们报名，露西。
- I was talking to my sandwich.
——我刚才在跟我三明治说话。
All right, just wait over there
好吧，就在那边等着
till we have enough players for two teams.
直到我们有足够的人分成两队。
- Are your brothers coming?
——你兄弟们会来吗？
- I hope not. I didn't tell them I was doing this.
——我希望不会。我没告诉他们我要参加这个。
For once, I'd like to be on a team
就这一次，我希望能在一个队伍里
with anyone whose name doesn't rhyme with "icky."
- They like their sister.
Is that so bad?
- They're good kids, Mae.
They mean well.
But I need some time away from them.
Lately, they've been sticking to me tighter
than honey to a frog's foot.
- That's not a thing.
- It is where I grew up.
- We grew up three blocks from each other.
我们从小就在相隔三个街区的地方长大。
- It hasn't gotten to you yet.
你还没感受到那种程度。
The point is, it's just kind of sad
关键是，他们对我依赖的程度有点让人难过。
how much they need me.
没有我，他们就一无所有。
Without me, they have nothing.
梅，那个可爱的男孩完全在盯着你。
[gasps] Mae, that cute boy is totally staring at you.
不，他没有。
- No, he's not.
哦，天哪！
Oh, my gosh!
那个可爱的男孩完全在盯着我。
That cute boy is totally staring at me.
我该怎么办？我该怎么办？
What do I do? What do I do?
交给我吧。
- Leave it to me.
- 交给我吧。
Put Mae on their team, okay?
- 让Mae加入他们的队伍，好吗？
- You're not the boss of me.
- 你又不是我的上司。
But your parents are, so fine.
- 但你的父母是，所以好吧。
- Maybe I'll get cute boys on my team too.
- 或许我也能招揽些帅气男孩到我的队伍里。
[both squealing]
[两人尖叫]
Hey.
嘿。
- So if you keep heading that way,
- 所以如果你继续往那个方向走，
you'll hit the bathrooms.
- 你会到达洗手间。
- Is it me, or were those boys handsome?
- 是我的错觉吗，那些男孩都很帅？
- Yes, they were.
是的，他们很帅。
Too bad they're not playing laser tag with me.
可惜他们没和我一起玩激光标签。
- Don't worry; we're here.
别担心，我们在这儿。
- Okay, awesome.
好的，太棒了。
We've finally got enough for two teams.
我们终于凑够人数组成两队了。
Mae, Jasper, and those guys
梅，贾斯帕，还有那些男生
versus Dawn and the Ickys.
对战 黎明和那些讨厌的家伙。
boys: Yay!
男生们：耶！
- Yay.
耶。
- Poor Dawn.
可怜的黎明。
She really needs us.
她真的很需要我们。
- Good thing we showed up.
幸好我们出现了。
- Or she'd have no friends to play with.
不然她就没有朋友一起玩了。
- You know, Dawn's a good kid,
你知道，Dawn是个好孩子，
but without us, she has nothing.
但没有我们，她什么都没有。
- [sighs]
[叹气]
[upbeat music]
[轻快的音乐]
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na ♪
- ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na na na na na na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- Dawn, I can't believe you blasted your own brothers.
- 道恩，我真不敢相信你对自己的兄弟们下手了。
- I just can't spend any more time with them, Mae. I had to put them out of my misery.
- 我实在无法再和他们相处下去了，梅。我不得不让他们从我的痛苦中解脱出来。
- Hey, Mae, I had fun playing with you.
- 嘿，梅，和你一起玩得很开心。
- You too, Jasper.
你也是，Jasper。
Hopefully we'll get to do it again soon.
希望我们很快能再一起玩。
- Hopefully next time, my brothers won't be here.
希望下次，我兄弟们不在。
Fingers crossed they got the message.
希望他们明白我的意思了。
- We got your message.
我们收到你的信息了。
- Oh, good, because I've been wanting to say something and I didn't know how to.
哦，太好了，因为我一直想说什么但又不知道怎么开口。
- No need to say anything.
不需要说什么。
I think we're all feeling it.
我想我们都感觉到了。
- It's pretty obvious.
这很明显。
- You're really bad at laser tag.
你在激光枪战里真的很差劲。
- But don't worry.
但别担心。
We're gonna practice with you every day until you get better.
我们会每天和你一起练习，直到你进步。
- Just try to get rid of us.
试试看甩掉我们。
- Yeah, we're gonna stick to you like honey to a frog's foot.
是啊，我们会像蜂蜜粘在青蛙脚上一样黏着你。
- What does that even mean?
那是什么意思？
- It means that wherever I go, they're there.
意思是我去哪儿，他们就在哪儿。
I get home; they're there.
我回家；他们在那儿。
I wake up; they're there.
我醒来；他们在那儿。
I go to school; they're there.
我去学校；他们在那儿。
- There, there.
在那儿，在那儿。
- I need to find a new activity that they'd never like.
我需要找到一个他们永远不会喜欢的活动。
- I'm in a ballet class.
我在上芭蕾舞课。
How about that?
怎么样？
- Ugh, I hate ballet.
呃，我讨厌芭蕾。
It's perfect!
太完美了！
They'll hate it even more.
他们会更讨厌的。
- Hey, Dawn.
嘿，Dawn。
Laser tag ended kind of quick,
激光标签结束得有点快，
but don't feel bad.
但别难过。
We found something to fill the time.
我们找到了填补时间的东西。
- Do you like puzzles and are ages eight and up?
- 你喜欢拼图吗？适合八岁及以上年龄的人。
Then good news!
那么好消息来了！
- This one's all sky.
- 这一幅全是天空。
4,000 pieces, and they're all blue.
4000片，而且全是蓝色的。
What's that sound, boys?
那是什么声音，孩子们？
Sounds like the fun train's leaving the station.
听起来像是乐趣列车正在离开车站。
all: Puzzle, puzzle, puzzle, puzzle!
大家：拼图，拼图，拼图，拼图！
[chanting continues]
[吟唱继续]
Puzzle, puzzle, puzzle, puzzle.
拼图，拼图，拼图，拼图。
Blue-blue!
蓝-蓝！
- [mouths words]
- [无声说话]
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- ♪ 哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦 ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦 ♪
- I think we lost them.
- 我想我们甩掉他们了。
- Dawn, relax.
- 黎明，放松点。
They weren't following us.
他们没有跟着我们。
- Don't kid yourself, Mae.
- 别自欺欺人了，梅。
They followed me out of the womb,
他们从我出生起就一直跟着我，
and they haven't stopped since.
而且从未停止过。
- You made us ride in my mom's trunk.
你让我们坐进了我妈车的后备箱。
I think we're good.
我觉得我们没事了。
- You're right.
你说得对。
This is a no-bro zone.
这里没有兄弟帮。
So...
所以...
let's ballet it up!
让我们跳起芭蕾吧！
- We don't really say that.
我们不这么说。
- Wow, that girl could bite her toenails.
哇，那女孩能咬到自己的脚趾甲。
- Oh, that's Eiffel.
哦，那是艾菲尔。
She's the best in the class.
她是班上最棒的。
She was the ballerina
她是那个芭蕾舞者
in that really funny toilet paper commercial.
在那则非常有趣的卫生纸广告中。
- Oh, The Butt-cracker? - Yeah!
- 哦，是《屁股碎纸机》？ - 对！
- Sweet!
- 太棒了！
All right, let me try.
好吧，让我试试。
- Wow, impressive.
- 哇，真厉害。
- Thanks, no biggie.
- 谢谢，没什么大不了的。
- You did it.
- 你做到了。
- I know. I think I'm a natural.
- 我知道。我觉得我有天赋。
Only one problem.
只有一个问题。
I can't get my leg down.
我没法把腿放下来。
- What? - My leg is stuck.
什么？我的腿卡住了。
Help me, help me, help me, help me! - Okay.
帮帮我，帮帮我，帮帮我，帮帮我！好的。
Help me, help me, help me, help me!
帮帮我，帮帮我，帮帮我，帮帮我！
Help me, help me, help me!
帮帮我，帮帮我，帮帮我！
♪ Oh ♪
哦
- Anne, I think I've got it.
安妮，我想我搞定了。
I have just the thing to put the wind
我正好有办法让我们的销售重新振作起来。
back in our "sale."
向斯奎西问好，
Say hello to Squishy,
销售犬。
the "sale-r" dog.
- I don't get it.
- 我不明白。
- What's not to get, Anne?
- 有什么不明白的，Anne？
We have a big, annual sale.
我们有一个大型的年度销售活动。
He's Squishy, the "sale-r" dog.
他是Squishy，销售犬。
'Cause he's dressed like a little sailor.
因为他打扮得像个小水手。
[high-pitched] Ahoy!
[高音] 啊哈！
- Tom, we need something that's gonna make people want to buy things.
- Tom，我们需要一些能让人想买东西的东西。
This is just gonna make people say, "Aww."
这只会让人们说，“啊啊。”
- Aww.
- 啊啊。
- Look, I've been going over the numbers,
- 你看，我一直在研究这些数据，
and the last time our sale was actually profitable
- 我们上一次销售真正盈利的时候，
was 12 years ago.
- 已经是12年前了。
- As I recall, that was our first foray into radio.
- 我记得，那次是我们第一次尝试电台广告。
You remember the jingle? - Oh, no.
- 你记得那首广告歌吗？
- ♪ Hurry on down to Tom's Get Sporty ♪
- 哦，不。
♪ Save 10%, which is close to 40 ♪
- ♪ 快来汤姆的运动用品店 ♪
♪ Take it from your old Uncle Morty ♪
- ♪ 省下10%，接近40块 ♪
♪ You'll save plenty at Tom's Get Sporty ♪
- ♪ 听你老叔叔莫蒂的话 ♪
- No, no, Uncle Morty was the year after our big success,
- ♪ 在汤姆的运动用品店省不少 ♪
and he was a horrible failure.
而且他是一个可怕的失败者。
- So what was 12 years ago?
那么12年前发生了什么？
- Well, we didn't do anything big that year,
嗯，那年我们没有做任何大事，
because I was pregnant.
因为我怀孕了。
- So the thing that was big was you.
所以那个大事就是你。
- Oh, it's true, though.
哦，确实是这样。
Every customer I waited on
每一位我接待的顾客
felt so much sympathy and support for me,
都对我充满了同情和支持，
they bought, like, anything I showed them.
他们几乎买下了我展示给他们的任何东西。
- It's too bad you're not pregnant again.
真可惜你不再怀孕了。
- Huh, I know.
- 嗯，我知道。
Wait a minute. What if I am?
等等。如果我真的是呢？
- What are you telling me, Anne?
- 你在告诉我什么，安妮？
- Oh, no, no. Honey, no, no, no. I'm not saying I am.
- 哦，不，不。亲爱的，不，不，不。我不是说我真的是。
I'm saying what if, um--oh--
我是说如果，嗯——哦——
I am?
我真的是呢？
Huh?
嗯？
- Whoa.
- 哇。
- Huh?
- 嗯？
- Oh, here. Here, here, here, here, sit, sit.
- 哦，来。来，来，来，来，坐，坐。
Can I get you anything?
需要我帮你拿点什么吗？
- Honey, honey, honey, it's a watermelon.
亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，这是西瓜。
- I'll love it no matter what it is.
无论是什么，我都会喜欢的。
- Okay.
好的。
- Hello?
喂？
Ickys?
Ickys？
[sighs] Coast is clear.
安全了。
- Thanks for bringing me home, Mae,
谢谢你带我回家，梅，
and helping me change,
还帮我换了衣服，
and scratching that itch.
还有挠那个痒。
- Dawn, it's been stuck like that for four hours.
- 道恩，它已经那样卡了四个小时了。
I think you should see a doctor.
我觉得你应该去看医生。
- I'm fine, Mae.
- 我没事，梅。
- Ugh, I feel so bad.
- 呃，我感觉很糟糕。
You didn't even want to go to ballet.
你甚至不想去上芭蕾课。
- No, I loved it.
- 不，我很喜欢。
I thought it would be boring, but it was totally fun.
我以为会很无聊，但真的很有趣。
The boys not being there was just a bonus.
那些男孩不在那里只是个额外的好处。
- Okay, well, see you tomorrow.
- 好吧，明天见。
- High five?
击掌？
- Oh.
哦。
- [grunts, sighs]
（咕哝，叹气）
- Hey, Dawn. - Oh!
嘿，Dawn。
- Where you been?
哦！
- Yeah, last time we saw you,
你去哪儿了？
you brought us all warm milk.
是啊，上次我们看到你，
- And then when we woke up, you were gone.
你给我们都带来了热牛奶。
- Oh, well,
然后当我们醒来时，你已经走了。
that milk knocked you guys right out,
哦，那牛奶让你们都睡着了，
and I didn't know what to do.
我那时不知道该怎么办。
So I wandered down here.
所以我就在这里徘徊。
Now I'm gonna wander back upstairs and take a shower.
现在我要回到楼上洗澡了。
Excuse me.
借过一下。
- Wow, without us, she seems so lost and confused.
哇，没有我们，她看起来好迷茫和困惑。
- Yeah, she can't even remember how to walk.
是啊，她甚至都不记得怎么走路了。
- Hey, Anne,
嘿，安妮，
these customers don't want these ski boots.
这些顾客不想要这些滑雪靴。
Could you put them back on the shelf?
你能把它们放回架子上吗？
- Oh, sure thing, sweetie.
哦，当然可以，亲爱的。
[sharply exhales]
[尖锐地呼气]
[sighing]
[叹气]
Yeah, you mean the-- the high shelf
是的，你是说那个...那个高架子
upstairs in the back?
在楼上后面吗？
- That's the one. - Okay.
- 就是那个。 - 好的。
- Be careful on that old ladder. You're climbing for two.
- 在那旧梯子上要小心。你现在是两个人在爬。
- Oh.
- 哦。
- You know what? Um, we'll take the ski boots.
- 你知道吗？嗯，我们要买这些滑雪靴。
- Great.
- 太好了。
- Are you also going to need skis, bindings, and poles?
- 你们还需要滑雪板、固定器和滑雪杖吗？
- I don't think so.
- 我不这么认为。
- That's okay; I'm just gonna lug them back upstairs.
- 没关系；我只会把它们搬回楼上。
- Oh, you know what? Um, we'll take it all.
- 哦，你知道吗？嗯，我们全都要了。
- Ah, great. - Yeah.
- 啊，太好了。 - 是的。
- Let's get you all ringed up.
- 让我们帮你全部结账。
[groans]
[呻吟]
[melodic whistling]
[旋律口哨]
[Nutcracker Suite plays]
[胡桃夹子组曲播放]
- Don't bend your elbows.
- 不要弯曲你的肘部。
Unclench your fists.
放松你的拳头。
Good.
好。
- Do I look like you now?
- 我现在看起来像你了吗？
- I said good, not Butt-cracker good.
- 我说好，不是指‘屁股开裂’那么好。
- Don't worry; I've been here six months,
- 别担心；我在这里已经六个月了，
and I'm still not "Butt-cracker good."
我仍然达不到‘屁股开裂’那么好。
- Oh.
- 哦。
- My.
- 我的。
- Gosh.
- 天哪。
She's doing ballet.
她在跳芭蕾舞。
- She hates ballet.
- 她讨厌芭蕾舞。
- I love ballet!
- 我爱芭蕾！
- Oh, poor Dawn.
- 哦，可怜的Dawn。
We weren't around, so she got lonely and followed Mae here.
我们不在，所以她感到孤独，跟着Mae来到了这里。
- So sad.
- 真可怜。
- She couldn't even go two hours without us.
- 她甚至不能离开我们两个小时。
- What?
- 什么？
Can you believe it, Mae? They're here.
你能相信吗，Mae？他们在这里。
They can't even go two hours without me.
他们甚至不能离开我两个小时。
- It looks like they want to come in.
- 看起来他们想进来。
- Please, don't. No!
- 请，不要。不！
- She said, "Please don't go."
她说：“请不要走。”
We came just in time.
我们来得正是时候。
- I'm gonna go out there and get rid of them.
我要出去把他们赶走。
What are you guys doing here?
你们在这里做什么？
- You know why we're here.
你知道我们为什么来这里。
We all know why we're here.
我们都知道我们为什么来这里。
- Yeah, I know why you're here,
是的，我知道你们为什么来这里，
but I'm pretty sure you can't be here.
但我很确定你们不能在这里。
You know, I think the teacher's not gonna want you here.
你知道，我想老师不会希望你们在这里。
- Wait, you boys want to join the class?
等等，你们想加入这个班级吗？
- Of course.
当然。
If our sister's here, then we are too.
如果我们的姐妹在这里，我们也会在这里。
- Fantastic!
太棒了！
I'll get you set up.
我会帮你们安排好的。
- But-- but no, they really don't want--
但是...但他们真的不希望...
- Aren't you glad these boys are here?
你们难道不高兴这些男孩们在这里吗？
Now I can finally showcase my true abilities.
现在我终于可以展示我的真正实力了。
Hold my waist.
搂着我的腰。
- She was talking to me.
她是在和我说话。
I'm Dicky. - I'm Eiffel.
我是迪基。- 我是艾菲尔。
- Don't sell yourself short.
别低估自己。
You're two eyefulls.
你们俩真是养眼。
[applause]
掌声
- You can thank us later.
你可以稍后感谢我们。
- I told you we should've ridden in your mom's trunk again.
我告诉过你我们应该再次坐你妈妈的后备箱。
But no, you had to have a seat belt.
但是不，你非要系安全带。
- Can't let me have my own thing.
就不能让我有自己的事吗。
Ballet wreckers.
芭蕾破坏者。
[blender buzzing]
搅拌机嗡嗡声
- Dawn?
Dawn？
Dawn! - Oh, what?
黎明！ - 哦，怎么了？
- Honey, you promised you wouldn't blend angry anymore.
- 亲爱的，你答应过我不会再生气地搅拌了。
- [sighs] - We talk about our problems.
- [叹气] - 我们应该谈论我们的问题。
We don't liquefy them.
而不是把它们搅成液体。
- I'm sorry.
- 对不起。
I went to ballet class to get away from the boys,
我去上芭蕾课是为了远离那些男孩，
but of course they just horned in on that too.
但当然他们也闯入了那里。
Just--it makes me want to just--
只是——这让我想——
- No, no, no, no, hey, hey, hey, hey.
- 不，不，不，不，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
- I'm sorry, but they're like little baby ducks.
- 对不起，但他们就像小鸭子一样。
You know, waddling behind me everywhere that I go.
你知道，就像小鸭子一样，摇摇摆摆地跟在我后面，无论我走到哪里。
I'm tired of being the mama duck.
我厌倦了当那只母鸭。
- Honey, do yourself a favor
亲爱的，帮自己一个忙
and tell your brothers the truth.
告诉你的兄弟们真相。
You'll feel better.
你会感觉好些的。
It is always best to be honest with people.
对人们诚实总是最好的。
[sighing]
（叹气）
- Hey, guys,
嘿，伙计们，
I have to tell you something.
我必须告诉你们一些事情。
I really, really love being a quad,
我真的，真的很喜欢当一个四轮车手，
but I'm also starting to love ballet,
但是我也开始爱上芭蕾了，
and I kind of want it to be my thing.
而且我有点想让它成为我的专长。
I hope this doesn't hurt your feelings too much.
希望这不会太伤你们的感情。
- I'm good.
- 我没事。
- Me too. - No sweat.
- 我也是。- 没问题。
- Oh, well, phew!
- 哦，那就好，呼！
Thanks for taking it so well, guys.
谢谢你们这么理解，伙计们。
- No worries. - Our pleasure.
- 没事的。- 我们的荣幸。
- We only went
- 我们去学芭蕾
to ballet 'cause you needed us.
只是因为当时你需要我们。
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇。
Let's be clear.
让我们说清楚。
I didn't need you.
我并不需要你们。
- Come on, Dawn. You always need us.
得了吧，Dawn，你总是需要我们。
- No, I'm the mama duck. You're the baby ducks.
不，我是母鸭，你们是雏鸭。
I waddle; you follow. Quack-quack!
我摇摇摆摆走，你们跟着。嘎嘎！
- No, we're the papa ducks.
不，我们是公鸭。
- Yeah, we waddle; you follow.
对，我们摇摇摆摆走，你跟着。
- Oh, please. You need me.
哦，拜托。你需要我。
- No, you need us.
不，你需要我们。
- I don't need you!
- 我不需要你！
- Well, we don't need you!
- 我们也不需要你！
- Quack!
- 呱！
- Oh, yeah? Quack, quack.
- 哦，是吗？呱，呱。
- Quack, quack, quack!
- 呱，呱，呱！
- Quack, quack, quackety-quack!
- 呱，呱，呱呱呱！
[all quacking]
[所有鸭子呱呱叫]
- Hey, you guys seen Mae?
- 嘿，你们看到梅了吗？
- Can't talk. - We're quacking here!
- 没空说话。 - 我们正在呱呱叫呢！
[quacking resumes]
[呱呱声继续]
- Ah, do you smell that, Mae?
啊，你闻到了吗，Mae？
- [inhales] I smell feet.
我闻到了脚的味道。
- Yes, but they aren't my brothers' feet.
是的，但那不是我兄弟们的脚。
I don't have to smell my brothers.
我不需要闻我兄弟们的脚。
I don't have to see my brothers.
我不需要看到我兄弟们。
I don't even have to hear the word "brothers."
我甚至不需要听到'兄弟'这个词。
- Where are your brothers?
你的兄弟们在哪里？
- Oh, don't worry. They won't be back.
哦，别担心。他们不会回来了。
- What? But we need them.
什么？但我们需要他们。
- Uh, for what?
呃，为了什么？
I don't know if you noticed,
我不知道你有没有注意到，
but they weren't very good.
但他们并不怎么样。
- I don't need them to be good.
- 我不需要他们有多好。
I need them to make me look good.
我需要他们让我看起来好。
If we don't have boys in the class,
如果我们班没有男生，
who's gonna partner with me for my pas de deux?
谁会和我搭档做双人舞呢？
- Well, I "a-pas-de-gize."
- 嗯，我“不会跳舞”。
but it looks like you're gonna have to pas de do it yourself.
但看起来你得自己跳了。
- Do you even know what "pas de deux" means?
- 你知道“双人舞”是什么意思吗？
- Pas de duh!
- 当然知道！
[both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
- Stop doing that. - Sorry.
- 别那样做了。 - 对不起。
- Look, you like this class, right?
- 看，你喜欢这门课，对吧？
- Yes.
- 是的。
- And you want to make it better, right?
- 而且你想让它变得更好，对吧？
- Of course. - Great.
- 当然。 - 太好了。
Then do us all a favor.
那么请帮我们大家一个忙。
Don't come back to class without your brothers.
没有你兄弟们，就不要再来上课了。
- Wait, what?
- 等等，什么？
- Hey, you may have been in a toilet paper commercial--
- 嘿，你可能拍过一个卫生纸广告——
- Two. You're looking at the new Snow Wipe.
- 两个。你们现在看到的是新的雪擦。
- Well, that doesn't make you better than anybody else.
- 那并不意味着你比别人优越。
- Actually, it does.
- 实际上，是的。
It also gives me free toilet paper for life.
它还让我终身免费使用卫生纸。
So boys, please.
所以，男孩们，请。
- Yeah, well, if she doesn't come back,
- 是啊，如果她不回来，
then I don't come back.
那我也不回来。
- All right, Mae.
- 好吧，梅。
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉。
We'll miss you.
我们会想念你的。
- Mae, this is all my fault.
- 梅，这都是我的错。
- Yes, it is.
- 是的，没错。
Sorry, that just came out.
对不起，这话脱口而出了。
I don't blame you-- yes, I do!
我不怪你——不，我确实怪你！
Sorry, the words just keep coming out--your feet smell!
对不起，话就是止不住——你的脚好臭！
I should go.
我该走了。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Anne, lookit.
- 安妮，看这儿。
Our big blowout sale is once again
我们的盛大促销活动再次
in the profit column
进入了盈利栏目
thanks to you and our little bundle
多亏了你和我们那堆没叠的衣物。
of unfolded laundry.
我们的小财神爷是谁？是你！
Who's my little moneymaker? You are!
你是我的小财神爷。
You're my little moneymaker.
我——你不觉得这有点内疚吗，汤姆？
- I--don't you feel guilty about this, Tom?
嘘！我正在数钱。
- Shh! I'm counting.
比以往任何时候都要多。
Higher than I've ever had to count before.
你知道，我给我们的女儿讲了一大通关于诚实的话，
- You know, I gave our daughter a big speech about being honest,
而我不知怎么的，就是觉得不太对劲。
and I don't know; I just haven't felt right about it since.
你为什么要跟她谈这个？
- Why did you talk to her?
这就是搅拌机的用途！
That's what the blender's for!
- What?
- 什么？
- So she can work through her problems on her own.
- 这样她就可以自己解决问题了。
Think about it Anne.
想想看，安妮。
If we make more money,
如果我们赚更多的钱，
we can buy all the kids blenders.
我们就可以给所有的孩子买搅拌机。
And then we won't have to talk to any of them.
那样我们就不用跟他们中的任何一个说话了。
- Tom, this-- this is just wrong.
- 汤姆，这——这不对。
- What are you saying, Anne?
- 你在说什么，安妮？
- I'm sorry, Tom. It's over. - Anne, no.
- 对不起，汤姆。结束了。 - 安妮，不。
- I can't be fake pregnant anymore
我不能再假装怀孕了
with your college sweatshirt baby.
用你的大学运动衫当宝宝。
- But, Anne, what about the sale?
但是，安妮，那销售怎么办？
- Tom, I can't.
汤姆，我做不到。
- Hey, guys.
嘿，伙计们。
So, look,
所以，听着，
Mae really needs you guys to come back to ballet.
梅真的需要你们回到芭蕾舞团。
- Oh, did you hear that, guys?
哦，你们听到了吗，伙计们？
Mae needs us to come back to ballet.
梅需要我们回到芭蕾舞团。
- Well,
那么，
what do you know?
那你知道吗？
Mae needs our help.
Mae需要我们的帮助。
- Poor Mae.
- 可怜的Mae。
We should really help Mae.
我们真的应该帮助Mae。
Why are we saying "Mae" like that?
我们为什么那样说'Mae'？
- 'Cause it's really Dawn who needs us.
- 因为实际上是Dawn需要我们。
- But didn't she say she didn't need us?
- 但她不是说她不需要我们吗？
- That's why we're saying "Mae" like that.
- 所以我们才那样说'Mae'。
- It really is for Mae.
- 这真的是为了Mae。
She stood up for me, and now the girls don't want us back
她为我挺身而出，现在那些女孩不想让我们回去
unless we show up with you boys.
除非我们和你们这些男孩一起出现。
So I guess you're right;
所以我想你是对的；
I do need you.
我真的需要你们。
- We knew it! - Was that so hard?
- 我们早就知道了！ - 有那么难吗？
- Look, I don't need you guys
- 听着，我不需要你们一直在我身边，
to be around me all the time,
但此刻，我需要你们做
but right now, I need you to do
任何自尊自爱的兄弟都会做的事。
what any self-respecting brother would do.
穿上紧身裤，踮起脚尖，
Slap on some tights, get on your tippy toes,
然后优雅地回到教室。
and pirouette back to class.
你们觉得怎么样？
What do you say?
你觉得怎么样？
- Don't worry, Dawn.
别担心，Dawn。
We'll be there for you.
我们会支持你的。
- Ah, thank you guys so much!
啊，太感谢你们了！
- Wow, she really does need us.
哇，她真的需要我们。
- Should we get our tights?
我们要不要穿上紧身衣？
- Nope.
不用。
We're gonna play laser tag.
我们要去玩激光对战。
[whispering] That's a nice fishing rod.
[低语]那是个不错的钓竿。
Shh, it's okay. Don't worry.
嘘，没关系。别担心。
Daddy's gonna sell this nice man a fishing rod,
爸爸要卖给这位好心人一根钓竿，
and then I'll be able
然后我就能
to finally buy you some baby food.
终于给你买些婴儿食品了。
- Tom!
汤姆！
- [imitates crying baby]
（模仿婴儿哭声）
Oh, great, Anne. You woke Pinny.
哦，安妮，你把平尼吵醒了。
Oh, he's so pale.
哦，他脸色好苍白。
Everyone, buy things!
大家，买东西吧！
That'll help!
那样会有帮助的！
- Tom? - Okay, okay.
汤姆？好的，好的。
You're right.
你说得对。
We shouldn't lie to our customers.
我们不应该对顾客撒谎。
- Don't worry, honey.
- 别担心，亲爱的。
I have just the guy who's gonna help
我正好有个能帮我们
make our sale a success.
成功促成销售的人。
[whistles]
[吹口哨]
- Sale-r dog! - Hi.
- 销售犬！ - 你好。
- It's a "sale-r" dog 'cause it's a--'cause it's a sale.
- 这是“销售犬”因为它是为了销售。
all: Aww!
大家：啊！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
- Okay, I got to ask.
好吧，我得问一下。
Are your brothers coming?
你兄弟们会来吗？
Are they not coming?
他们不来吗？
- They told me they'd be here,
他们告诉我他们会来的，
but I knew I couldn't count on them.
但我知道不能指望他们。
They're always around when I don't want them
我不要他们来的时候他们总在，
and never around when I do.
我需要他们的时候他们总不在。
I'm sorry, Mae.
对不起，Mae。
I've ruined this whole dance class for you.
我把你的整个舞蹈课都搞砸了。
- Oh, don't worry.
哦，别担心。
I'll just ruin something of yours.
我只会毁了你的一些东西。
- Oh, you're doing that thing again
哦，你又在那样做了，
when you say something and then take it back.
当你说些什么然后又收回。
- Nope.
不。
- So where are your brothers?
那么你的兄弟们呢？
- Oh, yeah, my brothers.
哦，对了，我的兄弟们。
Well, I talked to them, and--
嗯，我和他们谈过了，而且——
- We heard you loud and clear.
我们听得很清楚。
both: Oh, thank goodness.
我们都听到了，谢天谢地。
- We hear you've been giving our sister
- 我们听说你一直在给我们妹妹
and her friend a hard time.
和她朋友找麻烦。
- If you get boys back in the class,
- 如果让男生回到班上，
do you promise to be nice to them?
你能保证对他们友好吗？
- Yes, of course. I promise.
- 当然可以，我保证。
- Great, then we have a deal.
- 太好了，那我们就达成协议了。
- Why aren't you wearing your tights?
- 你为什么没穿紧身裤？
- Because we're not coming back. - What? - But you said we had a deal. - We do have a deal.
- 因为我们不回来了。 - 什么？ - 但你说我们达成协议了。 - 我们的确有协议。
- You need boys; we got you boys.
- 你需要男生；我们给你带来了男生。
- Boys!
- 男生们！
- Mae, you remember Jasper.
梅，你还记得贾斯珀吧。
- Hey, Mae, nice to see you.
嘿，梅，很高兴见到你。
- What did you do?
你做了什么？
- We got you boys.
我们给你带来了男孩们。
- That aren't us. - And who like Mae.
那不是我们。而且谁喜欢梅。
We get it, Dawn.
我们明白了，道恩。
You need some you time.
你需要一些自己的时间。
- And that's cool with us.
这对我们来说没问题。
- You know, I do like having time away from you guys,
你知道，我的确喜欢离开你们一段时间，
but it's also really nice to know
但知道在我需要时你们会在那里，真的很不错。
that you'll be there for me when I do need you.
当你真的需要我时，我知道你会在我身边。
- Always.
永远都会。
- Group hug?
来个集体拥抱？
- Nah, I think we all get it.
不了，我想我们都懂。
- All right.
好吧。
- Want to find some other kids and play some laser tag?
想找其他孩子一起玩激光标签吗？
- That sounds good to me.
听起来不错。
- I just have one question.
我只有一个问题。
How do I get out of this?
我怎么才能离开这里？
Help me, help me, help me, help me,
帮帮我，帮帮我，帮帮我，帮帮我，
help me, help me!
救救我，救救我！
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
- [whistling]
- [口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪